Neufeld, Maurice F. Collection of New York Times Clippings 5515
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Maurice F. Neufeld Collection of New York Times Clippings
1929-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Neufeld, Maurice F.
5515
27 cubic feet
27 linear ft.
Cippings (information artifacts), scrapbooks.
Clippings from the New York Times, collected by Maurice F. Neufeld.
5658977
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 14, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 14, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Professor Maurice Frank Neufeld (October 27, 1910 -April 10, 2003) was an American academic, author, union organizer and Army officer. In 1945, he was one of the two founding faculty members of the School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, appointed by its founding dean, Irving Ives.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5885: New York Times Additional Clipping File
Labor movement -- United States.; Labor unions -- United States; Neufeld, Maurice F.
5658977
- Labor Agriculture - Automobile, Aircraft (Box 1)
  - Labor Agriculture, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Labor Auto, Air & Agri. Implements, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Labor Agriculture, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Labor Auto, Air, & Agri. Implements, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Labor Auto Air & Agri. Implements, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Labor Auto, Air & Agri. Implements, 1952-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Labor Auto, Air & Agri. Implements & Aerospace, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Labor Auto, Air & Agri. Implements & Aerospace, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Labor Auto, Air & Agri. Implements., & Aerospace, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Labor Building Trades - Clothing, Women (Box 2)
  - Labor, Clothing - Women, 1960-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Labor, Clothing - Women, 1947-1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Labor, Clothing - Men, 1948-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Labor Chemical, Aromic Energy, Oil, 1946-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Labor Building Trades, 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Labor Building Trades, 1947-1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Labor Education (Box 3)
  - Labor Education, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Labor Education, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Labor Education, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Labor Education, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Labor Education, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Labor Education, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Labor Education, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Labor Education, 1946-1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Labor Electrical - Hotel, Restaurant (Box 4)
  - Hotel, Restaurant, Bar, Etc., 1946-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Labor Health and Welfare, 1959-1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Labor Health and Welfare, 1967-1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Labor Food and Allied Products, 1949-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Labor Electrical, Radio, Machine, 1962-1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Labor Electrical Radio & Machine, 1947-1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Labor Iron, Steel, Metal Trades (Box 5)
  - Labor Iron, Steel and Metal Trades, 1964-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Labor Iron Steel & Metal Trades, 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Labor Iron Steel & Metal Trades, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Labor Iron, Steel, & Metal Trades, 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Labor Iron, Steel, & Metal Trades, 1951-1955 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Labor Iron Steel & Metal Trades, 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Labor Mining-Music (Box 6)
  - Labor Music and Entertainment, 1960-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Labor Music and Entertainment, 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Labor Music and Entertainment, 1946-1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Labor Miscellaneous Industries and Trades, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Labor Mining Coal and Coke, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Labor Mining Coal and Coke, 1950-1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Labor Mining Coal and Coke, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Labor Mining Coal and Coke, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Labor Office-Services (Box 7)
  - Labor Newspapers, 1955-1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Labor Negro and Minority Groups, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Labor Negro and Minority Groups, 1961-1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Labor Newspapers, 1970-1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Labor Newspapers, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Labor Office Business, Professional, Services & Finance--General, 1948-1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Labor Office Business, etc, 1947-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Labor Other Countries, General-Other Countries, Asia, Far Eastern (Box 8)
  - Labor - International Federations, 1951-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Labor Other Countries Africa, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Labor Other Countries Africa, 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Labor Other Countries Asia, 1963-1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Labor Other Countries Asia General, 1962-1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Labor Other Countries, Asia, Near Eastern - Other Countries, Central and South America (Box 9)
  - Defense Mobilization and Agencies, 1951-1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Labor Other Countries U.S. Possessions and Territories Canada, 1963-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Labor Other Countries Central and South America, 1958-1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Labor Other Countries Central and South America, 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Labor Other Countries Central and South America, 1962-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Labor Other Countries Australasian, 1954-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Labor Other Countries Asia Near East, 1962-1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Labor Other Countries, Europe (Box 10)
  - England -2- Ireland, 1968-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - England -1-, 1947-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Labor Other Countries Europe, 1947-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Labor Other Countries Europe, 1948-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Labor Other Countries Europe, 1966-1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Labor Policy -Political Action (Box 11)
  - Labor Political Action, 1960-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Labor Political Action, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Labor Policy, 1946-1953 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Labor Policy (See also: 45-Wages and Hours), 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Labor Printing - Public Service (Box 12)
  - Labor Public Service, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Labor Public Service, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Labor Public Service, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Labor Printing and Publishing, 1959-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Labor Printing and Publishing, 1947-1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Labor Public Service, 1949-1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Labor Public Service, 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Labor Public Service, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Labor Telephone - Labor, Transportation, Electric and Street (Box 13)
  - Labor Transportation Electric & Street, 1951-1956 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Labor Transportation Electric & Street, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Labor Transportation Electric & Street, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Labor Transportation Air, 1963-1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Labor Transportation Air, 1948-1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Labor Textile & Textiles Products, 1948-1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Labor Telephone & Telegraph, 1963-1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Labor Telephone and Telegraph (Communications), 1947-1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Labor Transportation, Railroad (Box 14)
  - Labor Transportation Railroads, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Labor Transportation Railroads, 1967-1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Labor Transportation Railroads, 1963-1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Labor Transportation Railroads, 1951-1963 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Labor Transportation Railroads, 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Labor Transportation Electric & Street, 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Labor Transportation Electric & Street, 1966-1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Labor Transportation Electric & Street, 1957-1962 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Labor Transportation, Teamsters (Box 15)
  - Labor Transportation Teamsters, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Labor Transportation Teamsters, 1965-1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Labor Transportation Teamster, 1961-1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Labor Transportation Teamsters, 1957-1961 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Labor Transportation Teamsters, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Labor Transportation Teamsters, 1948-1957 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Labor Transportation Teamsters, 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Labor Transportation, Water and Longshoring - Union Staff Employees (Box 16)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1948-1951 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1954-1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Labor Transportation, Water, and Longshoring - Union Staff Employees (Box 17)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1963-1966 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Labor Transportation, Water and Longshoring - Union Staff Employees Socialism Strikes Wages (Box 18)
  - Labor Union Staff Employees, 1950-1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1970-1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Labor Transportation Water and Longshoring, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Strikes & Strike Legislation, 1946-1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Wages and Hour Legislation, 1947-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Wages and Hours, 1948-1966 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Socialism, Communism, ISMS, 1946-1955 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Socialism, Communism, ISMS, 1959-1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Labor Youth Movements (Box 19)
  - Youth Movements, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Youth Movements, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Youth Movements, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Youth Movements, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Youth Movements, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Youth Movements, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Youth Movements, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Youth Movements, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Youth Movements, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Labor Youth Movements (Box 20)
  - Youth Movements, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Youth Movements, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Youth Movements, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Youth Movements, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Youth Movements, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Labor Union Organization and Management (General), Administration - Organization Activities (Box 21)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - LUOM - Membership Rules & Justice Machinery (Closed Shop), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - LUOM - Finances and Dues, 1960-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management Locals, Meetings, Officers, Stewards, 1950-1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management International Unions, 1950-1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management; Organization, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management Joint Boards, Trade Councils, City Centrals, Etc., 1951-1954 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management Benefits and Insurance, 1957-1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management Administration and Operation, 1947-1954 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management General, 1948-1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - LUOM - Administration - Public Regulation, 1948-1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Labor Union Organization and Management Practices and Policies - Worker's Education (Box 22)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management International Affairs, 1950-1951 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management Leadership, 1966-1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management Leadership, 1951-1964 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - LUOM - Cooperatives, Housing and Banking, 1955-1958 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - LUOM - Workers Education and Apprenticeship, 1948-1967 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Labor Union Organization and Management State Federation and Councils, 1951-1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - LUOM - Public Relations, Community Service, and Government Cooperation, 1948-1967 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - LUOM - Practices and Policies (Juris. Disputes & Make Work, etc., 1945-1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Labor Union Organization and Management 1946-47 (See note on page one of Neufeld's original listing for explanation of Box 23) (Box 23)
  - 1946 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1946, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Labor - History, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Labor AFL-CIO and Other Federations (History), 1961-1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Labor - Political Action, 1946-1960 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Industry (General) Administration - Utilities (Box 24)
  - Industry - General, 1933-1947 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ind.- Administration + Organ, 1949-1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Industry - Agriculture, 1954-1972 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Industry - Associations, 1950-1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Ind. Auto, Air, Ag. Implements, 1947-1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Ind. Brewery + Beverages, 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Industry - Bldg. Trades, 1947-1949 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Industry - Chemical, 1946-1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Ind. - Clay. Glass, Stone, 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Industry - Clothing - Men, 1949-1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Industry - Clothing - Women, 1964-1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Ind.-- Consultants (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Industry - Development, 1946-1956 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Industry - Elec., Radio, Machine, 1948-1957 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Industry - Food + Allied Products, 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Industry - Headwear, 1966-1974 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Industry - Health + Welfare, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Ind.-- History, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Industry - Intl. Feds, 1947-1952 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Ind.-- Leadership, 1951-1961 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Industry Leather and Fur Products, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Ind.-- Iron Steel and Metal Trades, 1949-1964 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Industry Location, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Industry - Lumber, etc., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Industry - Mining Coal, 1946-1950 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Industry - Mining Metals, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Industry - Music + Entertainment, 1947-1964 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Industry - Negro, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Industry- Newspaper, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Industry - Office, Business, Professional, etc., 1970 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Industry - Other Countries - Europe, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Industry - Political Action, 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Industry - Printing + Publishing, 1949-1967 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Industry - Rubber, Plastics, etc., 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Industry - Shipbuilding, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Industry - Supervisory Personnel, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Industry - Telephone + Telegraph, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Industry - Textile and Textile Products, 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Industry Transportation - Air, 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Industry - Transportation - Electric + Steel, 1947-1970 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Industry - Transportation - RR, 1946-1966 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Industry - Teamsters, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Industry - Water and Longshoring, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - 1939-1948 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Industry AFL, National - Lumber (Box 25)
  - Labor: Agric., 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Labor--General, 1967-1976 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Labor--AFL--National, 1946-1952 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Labor--AFL-- State & City, 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Labor--Auto, Air, AGR. IMPL., Aerospace, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Labor--Brewery & Beverages, 1958-1973 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Labor--Building Trades, 1966-1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Labor-- Clay, Glass, Stone, 1948-1968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Labor--Clothing--Men, 1953-1967 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Labor--Clothing--Women, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Labor--CIO--National, 1946-1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Labor--CIO--State & City, 1946-1954 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Labor--Electrical, Radio & Machine, 1963-1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Labor Federal Unions, AFL-CIO, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Labor--Food & Allied Prods., 1955-1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Labor--Chemical, Atomic Energy, Oil, 1952-1960 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Labor--Lumber, Woodworking, Paper, Pulp, 1947-1975 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Labor--History, 1960-1973 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Labor--Iron, Steel, Metal Trades, 1949-1960 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - 1949-1960 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Labor--Education, 1965-1976 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Labor--Education, 1947-1970 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Labor--Furniture & Upholstery, 1949-1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Labor--Headwear, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Labor--Health & Welfare, 1960-1974 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Labor--History--Racketeering, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Labor--Hotel, Restaurant, Bar, 1959-1971 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Labor- Independent Groups, 1948-1952 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Industry Mining - Transportation (Box 26)
  - Labor--Mining--Coal & Coke, 1949-1955 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Labor--Mining--Metals, 1951-1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Labor - Miscellaneous Industries _ Trades, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Labor--Multi-National Corporations, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Labor--Negro & Minority Groups, 1965-1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Labor--Newspapers, 1950-1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Labor--Office, Bus., Prof., etc., 1949-1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Labor--Office, etc.-- Retail & Dept. Store, 1955-1963 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Labor-- Other Countries - Gen., Int. Feds & Orgs., 1962 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Scope and Contents
    1 Photograph
  - Labor--Other Countries, 1946-1976 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Labor--Policy, 1951-1964 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Labor-- Political Action, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Labor--Printing & Publishing, 1947-1957 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Labor-- Public Service, 1970-1976 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Labor-- Rubber, Plastics, Cork, 1949-1976 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Labor-- Shipbuilding, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Labor--Supervisory Personnel, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Labor--Telephone & Telegraph, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Labor: Textile & Textile Products, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Labor: Transportation -- Electric & Street, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Labor: Transportation -- Railroad, 1954-1963 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Labor: Transportation -- Teamsters, 1957-1976 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Industry Union Growth- Women Socialism Youth Movements (Box 27)
  - Labor--Transportation-- Water & Longshoring, 1941-1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Labor Union Growth, 1968-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Labor Utility Workers, 1949-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Labor--Women, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Socialism, Communism, Isms, 1966-1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Youth Movements, 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Youth Movements, 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Youth Movements, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Youth Movements, 1965-1969 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - LUOM Folder #1, 1950-1963 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - LUOM Folder #2, 1955-1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)